<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<type>CSH</type>
		<description>Language labels for extension 'ics_layar_service', table 'tx_icslayarservice_sources'.</description>
		<labelContext type="array">
			<label index=".description">Table description</label>
		</labelContext>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index=".description">Layar layer source content description.</label>
			<label index=".details">Each records describes a layer. Layer data is retrieved from the specified table and fields.</label>
			<label index="name.description">Contains the layer name used to uniquely identify this layer.</label>
			<label index="name.details">The layer name is used by the Layar API to identify the source.</label>
			<label index="source.description">Table used as provider for POI data.</label>
			<label index="page.description">System folder where the POI data is stored.</label>
			<label index="page.details">If no folder is selected, all records from the database table are read.</label>
			<label index="title.description">Field name containing the POI title.</label>
			<label index="line2_ts.description">TypoScript used to generate the second line of POI details.</label>
			<label index="line2_ts.details">The TypoScript definition is executed in the context of the POI record as a TEXT content object.</label>
			<label index="line3_ts.description">TypoScript used to generate the third line of POI details.</label>
			<label index="line3_ts.details">The TypoScript definition is executed in the context of the POI record as a TEXT content object.</label>
			<label index="line4_ts.description">TypoScript used to generate the forth line of POI details.</label>
			<label index="line4_ts.details">The TypoScript definition is executed in the context of the POI record as a TEXT content object.</label>
			<label index="attribution_ts.description">TypoScript used to generate the attribution line of POI details.</label>
			<label index="attribution_ts.details">The TypoScript definition is executed in the context of the POI record as a TEXT content object.</label>
			<label index="actions.description">TypoScript used to generate the action's URIs.</label>
			<label index="actions.details">The TypoScript definition is executed in the context of the POI record as a TEXT content object. The resulting content MUST be a list of URIs. The separator is the comma. An empty URI is ignored with its same index label.</label>
			<label index="actions_label.description">TypoScript used to generate the action's labels.</label>
			<label index="actions_label.details">The TypoScript definition is executed in the context of the POI record as a TEXT content object. The resulting content MUST be a list of labels. The separator is the comma. An empty label is ignored with its same index URI.</label>
			<label index="image.description">Field name providing a picture illustrating the POI or the path to the picture.</label>
			<label index="image.details">The path can be recognized as full URL, absolute URL, site root relative path, or an uploaded file name. The last case works only if the path comes from a field.</label>
			<label index="type.description">Field name containing the POI type or its value.</label>
			<label index="type.details">The value can only be in the range 0 to 3 inclusives.</label>
			<label index="coordinates.description">Field name(s) containing the coordinates. Names are separated by comma.</label>
			<label index="coordinates.details">If only one field name, the field contains the latitude and the longitude in degrees separated by a comma. If two field names, the first field is the latitude in degrees and the second is longitude in degrees.</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
	<orig_hash type="array">
	</orig_hash>
	<orig_text type="array">
	</orig_text>
</T3locallang>